Brian Yoon

byoonweb3@gmail.com | http://www.linkedin.com/in/brian-yoon-gm | https://github.com/thinkaboutmovies | https://thinkaboutmovies.netlify.app/

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

Full-stack web developer who loves NFT's and web3 technologies. My experience exploring the web3 landscape guides me in everything that I do: making decisions in fast-paced development environments and tunneling down on high priority problems in ambiguous situations. I am self-taught on all things web3 which has trained me to always be learning, keep pushing out of my intellectual comfort zone, and constantly reach out to other collectors for data analysis. Some of my favorite NFT/Crypto people include Richerd.eth, DCLBlogger, The DeFi Edge, and 0xBender. My favorite NFT projects include The Metakey, Creature World, RTFKT Studios, Treeverse, Veefriends, Azukis, and Doodles.

TECHNICAL & INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

Languages: JavaScript, Python, HTML, CSS, SQL, Mongo, JSON

Libraries and Frameworks: React, Node.js, Express.js, Django, Jquery, Bootstrap, Databases and other: PostgreSQL, MongoDB, RESTful Routing, JSON API **Interpersonal skills:** Listening, Questioning, Problem-Solving, Public Speaking

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

Rotating Art Gallery - GitHub | Deployed App - React | CSS Grid | Framer Motion | Modulenft API Dynamically view your NFTs like a rotating art gallery.

- Implemented a search bar to a input wallet address or an Opensea account name to look at a wallet's NFTs
- Created arrow buttons to manually view specific NFTs if user wants to find a specific token
- Automated the rotation of NFTs being viewed so the user can have a frictionless experience

Pomodoro App - GitHub | Deployed App - React | Mongoose | Node.js | Express.js

Time yourself to stay focused and motivated when studying or working.

- Built a Task List section to add, delete, or edit tasks the user needs for their work.
- Established a Metrics Container section to see how many study sessions and breaks have been completed.
- Assemble a timer that can start, stop, and repeat so the user can notice time left until a session ends.

EXPERIENCE

The Metakey **Community Ambassador**

Remote 10/2021 - Present

- Advocate community ideas about partnership integrations back to the main office team
- Inform the community on the latest developments from the main office team
- Onboard new NFT holders on everything the Metakey has to offer

Marugame Udon **Crew Member**

Los Angeles, CA

08/2021 - 12/2021

- Provided quality guest service while articulating food integrity to each Marugame Udon guest
- Operated many work stations including seimen, tempura, yusen, musubi, dishes, and cash register
- Worked as a team player to fill in at understaffed stations while working at my own station

EDUCATION

General Assembly

Los Angeles, CA

Description of program

Completion: 04/2022

12-week intensive course that builds fluency in full-stack web development with an emphasis on a work-ready skill set

Santa Monica College

Los Angeles, CA 09/2019 - Present